like said welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
world to keep brother
Tel and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which had brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou shall have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
into thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in water under the Earth thou
shall not bow down thyself to them nor
serve them for the Lord thy God I'm a
jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and Sh any Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
take up his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shall th lab and do all thy work but the
seven day is is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God and it thou shall not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
that man servant nor thaty maid servant
nor thy cattle nor that stranger that is
within thy gates for six days the Lord
made Heaven and Earth the sea and all
that in them is and rested the seven day
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day and hollowed it honor thy father and
thy mother that thy days may be long
upon the land which the Lord thy God
give thee thou shall not kill thou shall
not commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou sh not bear false witness against
thy neighbor thou sh not cover thy
neighbor's house thou sh not cover thy
neighbor's wife nor his man servant nor
his maid servant nor his Ox nor his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors we
read Exodus 21 through1 17 and may the
Lord have a blessing to the reading of
his words in Jesus name we pray pray
amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all B questions will not be answered and
all along scripture questions will not
be answered for time's sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling the office so please be direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just asking that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum let
me introduce to you the family that's on
the panel this evening
got brother
Jerome R and peace Brother Julius good
evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother
tanzel good evening sister Deborah good
evening brother Sean good evening and we
have the guest caller with us and I'm
brother Cornell let us begin with our
first question this evening
yes there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A Malik
secure asked for you to explain John 7
verse
39 what is the holy ghost that wasn't
given to Jesus yet what is the holy
ghost that wasn't given to Jesus Yet
brother Jerome share some light
um the verse actually is referring to um
what wasn't given to the apostles yet
not Jesus okay but let's go read the
verse um John 7 and
okay get it go ahead but this spake he
of the spirit which they that believed
on him till
receive for the Holy Ghost was not yet
given because that Jesus were not yet
yet
glorified yeah
see this Holy Ghost is going to be the
spirit that the Lord going to send it's
going to lead and guide you in all truth
okay and the Lord said it's expedient
that I go if I go not away he won't come
unto you but if I go away I'll send him
unto you and his job is to lead and
guide you in all truth okay um let's go
uh to that John 16 verse
7 you get it go ahead and read
nevertheless I tell you the truth it is
expedient for you that I go away for if
I go not away The Confidant would not
come unto you but if I depart I will
send him unto
you okay and so in the St John go to the
14th chapter and read verse 26
but the comforter which is the Holy
Ghost whom the father will send in my
name he shall teach you all things and
bring all things to your remembrance
whatsoever I have said unto you yeah
because the Lord himself he was the
comforter and leading and guiding the
apostles but when he went away after his
resurrection and was glorified then the
Holy Ghost that's going to do this job
uh he going to be sent so let's go to uh
uh acts the first the first
chapter acts the first chapter and read
verse four and 5 and we going to
skip go ahead and being assembled
together with them commanded them that
they should not depart from Jerusalem
but wait for the promise of the Father
which said he ye have heard of me for
John truly baptized with water but ye
shall be baptized with the Holy Ghost
not many days hence yeah and it's
actually was going to take place on the
day of Pentecost Skip and read verse
eight and then we'll go to acts
two but you shall receive power after
that the Holy Ghost has come unto you
and ye shall be Witnesses unto me both
in Jerusalem and in all Judea and the
Samaria and un the utmost parts of the
earth and I go to the second chapter and
read verse 1 and
4 and when the day of Pentecost was
fully come they were all with one Accord
in one place and they were all filled
with the Holy Ghost and began to speak
with other tongues as the spirit gave
them
utterance y that's all I got
on all right yes sir so we know that
that couldn't have been Jesus because
the spirit was given to him without
measure all right thank you for for that
brother as we continue to move on to our
next question yes moving on we can talk
right here says it seems like man was
made twice from Genesis 1 vers 27 and 28
it says human was created but in Genesis
2 verse S it says it again can you
explain
all right brother Dre let's talk right
here as you share some light brother
yeah let's go to that Genesis one and
we're gonna read verses 27 and 28
Genesis 1 start at 26
tan go ahead and read it when you get
and God said let us make man in our
image after our likeness let them have
dominion over the fish of the sea and
over the fowls of the air and over the
cattle and over all the Earth and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the
Earth so God created man in his own
image in the image of God created he him
male and female created he them and God
blessed them and God said unto them be
fruitful and multiply and replenish the
Earth and subdue it and have dominion
over the fish of the sea and over the
fowls of the air and of every living
thing that moveth upon the Earth we see
here that God is
saying that you know he created man in
his own image in the image of God
created he him now let's go over to
Genesis
2 different creation and it's not him
doing it twice he's just giving us some
detail here so start at verse four
instead of
uh I think they wanted to start at at uh
at verse seven let's started read verse
four and and then we'll we'll go on from
there go ahead brother these are the
generations of the heavens and the Earth
and they were created and the day that
the Lord God made the earth and the
heavens see this is what he's telling
you here this is the generations like
Generations have multiple meanings like
you could talk about Generations being
the generations
of of a group of
people that folks descended from but
this generation is dealing with a
particular time frame that God did
something but go ahead read some more
and every plant of the field before it
was in the earth and every herb of the
field before it grew for the Lord God
had not caused it to rain upon the Earth
and there was not a man to teal the
ground so he going back before Man was
created and he's breaking it down here
in the second chapter go ahead brother
but there went up a mist from the earth
and water the whole face of the
ground and the Lord God form man of the
Dust of the ground and breathe into his
nostril the breath of life and Man
became a living
soul and so this is this is what this is
talking about here read verse eight
brother and that'll be it and the Lord
God planed a g e and there he put the
man whom he had formed right this is the
same man that we talking about in the
first chapter so hope that that answers
your question he's dealing with the
generations and he going back and giving
you a little bit more detail here in the
second
chapter that's all throw something in
absolutely yeah you know go to Genesis
the fth chapter and start reading at at
at verse one see the first chapter of
Genesis didn't mention a name it just
says man and the second chapter of
Genesis mention a name Adam so go to
five and one and and that'll put it
together for you yes
sir and this is the book of the
generation of Adam and the day that God
created man in the likeness of God made
him there it is go ahead male and female
created he them and blessed them and
called their name Adam in the day when
they were
created that included both chapters
didn't
[Music]
it the reason I'm saying this because in
the old days they used to teach among
Israelites that there was two
Creations there ain't but one that fifth
chapter puts it together that's
right yes sir all right thank you for
that add on we hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
the next yes moving on
ah says my uncle got caught up in a bad
Doctrine and is basically living by
Isaiah 14 verses 1 and two and
Revelation 13: 9 and 10 are those verses
talking about God's recompense
all right so with these two verses here
Isaiah 141 and2 and Revelation 139 and10
we ask brother Julia share some light
brother this is talking about this is
talking about the prophecy of when the
Lord
return
and the reward of the Saints let's go to
Genesis Isaiah 14 uh very quick uh
brother
tzel uncle got caught up in bad Doctrine
bad Doctrine is hatred against the
Gentiles and if he's living by that he
GNA have to change that that's a very
popular old teaching and you might well
get it in your mind sisters and brothers
the Lord say my house should be called a
house of prayer for all
people Genesis 141 and2 let's look what
the book say go ahead for the Lord will
have mercy on Jacob and he would choose
Israel and set them in their own land
and the strangers shall be joined with
them and they shall cleave to the house
of Jacob and they shall cleave to the
house of Jacob remember that go ahead
and the people shall take them and bring
them to their place and the house of
Israel shall possess them in the land of
the Lord servants and handmaid and they
shall take them captive who captives
they were and they shall rule over their
oppressors now that's this is somebody
talking about this is somebody thinking
that you going to rule over their
oppressors like the Gentile
and the other nations that ruled over us
but this is a different type of
rulership when the Lord return let me
show you what I'm talking about let's go
to Isaiah the 60th chapter real quick
Isaiah chapter
60 Isaiah chapter 60 brother Tel and
when you get it my
brother begin reading at verse 9 and 10
Isaiah 69 And1 this is the same time
once the Lord return Isa 69-10 go ahead
surely the ow shall wait for me and the
ships of tarus first to bring thy sons
from far and their silver and their gold
with them unto the name of the Lord thy
God and to the Holy One of Israel
because he hath glorify thee go ahead
brother and the sons of the strangers
shall build up thy walls and their kings
shall Minister unto thee for in thy
wrath I smoke thee but in my favor have
I had mercy on thee how did he have
mercy brought us back to the land now
this is the sons of the stranger this
what you going to do let's go to Ezekiel
the 47th
chapter Ezekiel the 47th chapter it
ain't going to be like it was in this
creation when the Lord uh uh when the
people have oppressed us we're going to
rule over them in righteousness Isaiah
21-23 Isaiah 47 21-23 go ahead Isaiah or
Ezekiel I'm sorry Ezekiel Ezekiel 47
21-23 thank
you so shall ye divide this land unto
you according to the tribes of Israel
yes and it shall come to pass that ye
shall divide it by lot for inheritance
unto you to the stranger that sour among
you yes which shall beg got children
among you and they shall be unto you as
born in the country among the children
of Israel you going to treat them as
equals go ahead they shall have
inheritance with you you among the
tribes of Israel uhhuh that shall come
to pass and then what tribe The Stranger
sourth there shall ye give him his
inheritance sayeth the Lord God because
they goonna be among us and you got to
give them their
inheritance last place Ephesians 3 and
and and verse 6 Ephesians 3 and verse 6
let's look at what Paul said about this
Ephesians 3 and verse
6 it ain't going to be like we think it
going to be uh is where we going to rule
over them with harshness no that ain't
happening Ephesians 3 and verse 6 go
ahead T that the Gentiles shall be
fellow Hees and of the same body and
partakers of his promise in Christ by
the gospel so now the Gentiles gonna
have his part and you gonna give him his
part and you gonna give him his
inheritance because they gonna dwell
among you the the the next question
about that he lives by Revelation the
13th chapter that can't be because this
is talking about the Great Tribulation
period Revelation 13 read vers 9 and
10 If any man have ears to hear have an
ear let him hear uhuh he that leadth
into captivity shall go into captivity
he that kth with the sword must be
killed with sword here is the patience
and the faith of the Saints so now this
is talking about the reward of the
Saints those that mess with you God
going to deal with them he going to
bring drama upon them that Great
Tribulation is when the Lord
return after that's why the Lord said
those that come through Great
Tribulation these are they that came
through Great Tribulation they overcame
the Great Tribulation so now whatever
happened to them the Lord going to exact
Vance on them that's why the Great
Tribulation he the day of the Lord is
the wrath of God upon those that oppress
this Saints that's all I got up on there
they a got nothing to do about how we
going to oppress The Strangers I hope
that helped uh
Cornel all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer their question
as we continue to move on to our next
question uh yes little mama hay says the
sacrifice of the red helper to usher in
the third temple being built is that a
pagan belief my understanding is that
Jesus was the ultimate sacrifice and she
gives uh reference to
numbers
19 all right she give reference to
numbers 19 go there brother tanzel and
we go ask a guest caller to share some
light from
there numbers 19 is a big book right and
she doesn't give I don't know if that's
the book or verse so right but I will
answer the question
question thing is no is not a uh H uh
what they what the are doing
over there is not a
pagan uh uh uh ritual it's something is
something that is a pagan belief it is
something it is a belief of it is
unbelief because when it come to the red
heer the red heer had nothing to do with
the dedicating of the Temple the red
heer and and and the solution made out
out of her ashes and also with the blood
was what was used to forgive people for
sin now what I do agree with the uh uh
uh call is that Jesus uh replaced that
because when Jesus died he did away with
all animal sacrifice let's go into
Hebrews the 10th chapter read verse one
then skip down and read verse four and
five and we're going to skip
to couple other places after that
Hebrews
1 then we're going to skip to four
five for the law having a shadow of good
things to come and not the very image of
the things can never with those
sacrifices which they offer year by year
continually make the com there unto
perfect for it is not possible that the
blood of bulls and of goats should take
away sin
that's why go
ahead wherefore when he cometh into the
world he say sacrifices and offerings
thou wouldest not but a body as thou
prepared
me verse
10 and by the which will we are
Sanctified through the offering of the
body of Jesus Christ once for
all now get down and read verse 12
but this man after he had offered one
sacrifice for sins forever sat down on
the right hand of
God read
verse go back to verse
eight
18 now where remission of these is there
was no more offering for
sin see and that's what this the the
aners of the red heer was for and the
blood it was for a sin offering and had
nothing to do with
dedicating so you get the people over
there that call themselves Jews then
they they don't understand that either
because the Lord say he showed his word
to Israel and his statute to Jacob he
haven't done that with any other Nation
so no it's not a pagan belief it is a
exercise
of of a uh nonbelief non understanding
that's all I have to say all right right
thank you for that we hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
yes moving on and the time is
755 Victorious SM asks what are the
Lord's sore
judgments the Lord's sword judgments
what are they brother
Julius the four the four sword judgments
when the land sins against when the
people in the land sins against the god
of Israel let's go to Ezekiel the 14th
chapter brother
tzel Ezekiel 14th
chapter and pick it up at verse
13 go ahead brother son of man when the
land sinth Against Me by trespassing
grievously then will I stretch out my
hand upon it and will break the staff of
the bread thereof and will send famine
upon it and will cut off man and Beast
from it verse 21
please for thus say the Lord God how
much more when I send my for sword
judgment upon Jerusalem The Sword and
the famine and the noan Beast and the
pestilence to cut off from it man and
Beast so now there when the Lord what is
this for sword judgment the sword the
famine the noisome beast and and the
pestilence that is how the Lord deal
with uh uh PE the people in the land
that sin against
them so that four sword judgments is the
sword the famine the noome pestilence
and the uh noome Beast the PES and no
all this stuff a lot of this stuff come
from
war you can see what's going over going
on in Ukraine and what's going on uh
over in uh in in uh Israel in that area
uh with her M so you see seeing some
judgments going on but the Lord uses
those four sore judgments when the land
s when the people in the land sin
against them that's all I
got all right thank you for that
Brothers we continue to move on to our
next question yes moving on MC says I
want to be baptized the right way but my
husband says he don't believe he doesn't
believe I have to get baptized again
will I be wrong for being baptized the
right way he goes to a Baptist Church
and I
stopped all right well nobody is ever
wrong for being baptized the right way
especially when they're going to walk
therein that is the key let's go to uh
Philippians the second chapter
Philippians chapter
2 and let's pick it up at verse 10
because there is one God that everybody
the righteous and the wicked is going to
have to bow before pick it up at that
verse 10 and go ahead brother that at
the name of Jesus every KNE should bow
of things in heaven and things in Earth
and things under the Earth uhhuh that
every tongue should confess that Jesus
Christ is Lord to the glory of God the
Father that's right the Jesus that came
and died for the sins of the whole world
go
ahead well for my beloved as ye have
always obey not as in my presence only
but now much more in my absence to work
out your own salvation with fear and
trembling uhhuh for it is God which
worketh in you both to Will and to do of
his good pleasure and it is God which
worketh in us and his will that we be
baptized right way and serve him with
all our heart turn over to acts the 2
chapter acts the second
chapter because the god that we are
reading about he is he is the god of the
seventh day which is the Sabbath day
which is also known as
Saturday so let's go into acts two and
let's see what it is that Peter had to
say and he was right there with the Lord
so let's see what he had to say say and
pick it up at that verse uh 36 brother
go ahead so therefore let all the house
of Israel knowth surely that God ha made
that same Jesus whom you have crucified
both Lord and Christ that this is the
right one go ahead now when they heard
this they were pricked in their heart
and said unto Peter and to the rest of
the Apostles men and Brethren what shall
we do what did Peter say well Peter said
unto them repent and be baptized every
one of you in the name of Jesus Christ
for the remission of sins and you shall
receive the gift of the Holy Ghost this
is the way that we are supposed to be
baptized in the name of Jesus not the
name of the Father the Son and the Holy
Ghost those are titles but done the
right way read keep read for the promise
is unto you and to your children and to
all that are far off even as many as the
Lord Our God shall call uhhuh and with
many other words did he testified and
exort saying save yourselves save
yourselves from this unto generation yes
one more verse then they gladly receive
his word were baptized and the same day
there were added unto them about 3,000
Souls yeah so being baptized the right
way hey is the way that Jesus prescribed
even down throughout the generations and
um if your heart's desires to get
baptized the right way as you said in
your question hey we'll be glad to honor
that for you you have to serve the Lord
with all your heart in getting baptized
that's part of the requirement and keep
his Commandments that's all I
got I wanted some input yes sir go right
ahead but first first thing is that
people don't the people don't understand
Jesus when he said go you in all Na Go
you teaching all nation and baptized in
the name of the father and in the name
of the son and in the name of the Holy
Ghost the word name so when they said I
baptize you in the name of the Father
the name of the son and the name of the
Holy Ghost then they are quoting Jesus
but they not obeying Jesus because uh
everywhere you look in the book they
baptized uh uh uh uh in the name of
Jesus did you read Acts 19
chapter um no we can go go there now
Acts
19 uhhuh all
right and read from one uh uh uh uh
six yeah because four picks up being
baptized in uh
Jesus right and in the meantime I want
somebody to grab the scripture where the
Lord says uh uh
uh uh I come in my father's name and
somebody else grab the scripture right
quick where he said and he will pray to
the father and he will send you the Holy
Ghost in his name so the people will
understand maybe her husband will
understand all right yeah that's John
five 19 first
okay Acts
19 and it came to pass that while apoll
was at Corinth
Paul having passed through the upper
Coast came to Ephesus and finding
certain disciples and he said unto them
have you received the Holy Ghost since
ye believe and they said unto him we
have not so much as heard whether there
being Holy Ghost and he said unto them
unto what then were ye baptized and they
said unto John the
Baptist then he said Paul John B
baptized with the baptism of repentance
saying unto the people that they should
believe on him which should come after
him that is on Christ
Jesus when they heard this they were
baptized in the name of the Lord
Jesus and when Paul had laid hands upon
them the Holy Ghost came on them and
they spake with tongues and
prophesied enough they were baptized the
name of Jesus now go what's that the
fifth chapter and see whose name
uh uh Jesus came in somebody had the
scripture right
quick John 5 and
43 I come in my father's name and ye
receive me not if another shall come in
his own name him ye will
receive okay so he say come in his
father's name and somebody find right
quick where you gonna pray to the father
they going to send the Holy Ghost in his
name that's John 14 mhm
and
Read John 14 uh
John 15 yeah if you love me keep my
Commandments and I will pray the father
and he shall give you another comforter
that he may abide with you
forever even the spirit of Truth whom
the world cannot rece see because it
seeth him not neither know of him but ye
but ye know him for he dwelleth with you
and shall be in
you that's not what I'm looking for
26 15 and
26 read
it but when The Confident is come whom I
will send unto you from the father even
the spirit of Truth which proceeded from
the father he shall testify of
me still not what I'm looking for verse
16 is I will pray the father and he
shall give you another
comforter no okay that's why you say I
pray the father and he will send you the
holy ghost in my
name it's most important
you all right when search mode for
that in the meantime you can go back to
Acts 2 and
38 no we we got enough on on that I just
want to get this see because being that
I used to be a Baptist I understand yeah
John
14 I think it's John 14 and
26 John 14 and 26 try that one t yeah
but the confident which is the Holy
Ghost whom the father will send in my
name there you go that's it he shall
teach you all things and bring all
things to your remembrance whatsoever I
have said unto
you right so so that's where the that's
what the era is he didn't know know that
the father Jesus came in the father's
name that mean the father's name was
Jesus and being he came in the father's
name Jesus name Jesus and he turned
around and sent you to Holy Ghost and
his sent us the Holy Ghost in in jesus'
name that mean he come in the name of
Jesus so if you're going to baptize
correctly you simply say I baptize you
in the name of Jesus therefore then you
have obeyed the Commandment of that
Jesus gave when he said baptized in the
name of the father Son and the Holy
Ghost that's
right you have to call the name over and
the name is Jesus amen that's all I have
to say all right and uh we hope that uh
your husband received that message and
y'all get baptized the right way
together all right that's all we got on
that and um sister Deborah next question
next question and the time is
8:07 Miss Wade ask in scripture Hebrews
12 verse 23 to the spirit of just men
made perfect mean what all right brother
Julius share some light on that question
let's go to Hebrews
12 let's read
that Hebrews 12 and verse 23 now I want
you to pick it up uh to ver at verse
22 okay for ye are come unto Mount Sion
and unto the city of the Living God the
heavenly Jerusalem and to the
innumerable company of angels
go ahead to the general assembly and
Church of the firstborn which I written
in heaven and to God the judge of all
and to the spirit of just men made
perfect how did just men righteous men
become perfect let's go to Matthew 19
Matthew
19 and see what makes you perfect
Matthew 19 and we goingon to pick this
up at verse 16
when you get it my brother go ahead and
behold one came and said unto him good
Master what good thing shall I do that I
may have eternal life uhuh and he said
unto him why call thou me good there is
none good but one that is God but if
thou will enter into life keep the
Commandments and that's how that's what
justifies you and that's what makes you
perfect one more place James
1 James
1 and look what we got to do to maintain
that James 1 and pick it up at verse 12
James 1 and 12 when you get it tzel go
ahead and read it blessed is the man
that endureth Temptation for when he is
tried he shall receive the Crown of
Life had promised to them that love
him skip down to verse 21 and read
it wherefore lay part all filthiness and
superfluity of naughtiness and receive
with meekness the engrafted word which
is able to save your souls so we're
talking what's able to save your soul is
making you that's gonna make you God
only god is perfect so now just being
made perfect all that means is that you
got to overcome the world you got to
overcome yourself you got to keep the
Commandments and be obedience to the law
statutes and Commandments of God and
that is what's going to make you perfect
endure through your faith through your
righteousness and your faith and you
will until your end until the end and
that's what's going to make you just a
perfect man or a woman that's all I
got right brother Julius just follow
Christ right hey let let me throw
something in yes
caller yeah he said perfect only god is
perfect that's why Jesus would even
allow him called good because he was in
the flesh but some people told him
Jesus uh uh that Herod was going to kill
him he said I want you to tell Fox Herod
to the day Healing The Sick and uh uh um
and I think is uh uh cast out
devils and the third day I will be made
perfect oh you got the scripture if you
can't read
it that it be luke 13 and let's pick it
up at that verse 32 I believe Luke 13
and let's see go tell that fox
yeah all right Luke 13
and
32 uh
start pick it up yeah pick it up at 30
which one did you say 31 yeah yeah pick
it up there bro
yep the same day there came certain of
the Pharisees saying unto him get thee
out and depart hence for Herod will kill
thee and he said unto them but go ye
tell that fox behold I cast out devils
and I do cure today and tomorrow and the
third day I shall be
perfect okay what happened what what
happened to him on the third day he
resurrected he rose from the dead and
that's when he became God that's when he
became okay yes sir thank
you all right all right good add on hope
that answered your question next
question sister yes at the time is 812
Stephen Gus asks in Deuteronomy 14 verse
one ye are the children of the Lord your
God ye shall not cut yourselves nor make
any baldness between your eyes for the
dead what is making baldness between the
eyes guys all right brother Dre what you
say yeah that that's
cutting a lot of lot of people cut
themselves they did different things but
let's go read that Deuteronomy 14 and
one read that brother when you get it ye
are the children of the Lord your God
you should not cut yourselves nor make
any bers between your eyes for the dead
so Servants of God should not be doing
this but this is they did when they were
in mourning let's go to Jeremiah 16 and
look at something there Jeremiah
16 and just read verse 6 Jeremiah 16
and6 go
ahead both the Great and the small shall
die in this land that shall not be
buried neither shall men lament for them
nor cut themselves nor make themselves
bald for
them go ahead neither shall men tear
themselves for them in mour to comfort
them for the dead either shall men give
them the cup of consolation to drink for
their father or for their mother oh a
lot of people this is what they did in
their ritual of mourn they
lamented and in their mourning and
lamentation they will cut themselves
some Nations to this day you see them
with gashes on their face some of them
put them in between their
eyebrows yeah their heads so that is
something that the Lord did not have the
children of Israel
do and there's a Litany of other
scriptures that tell you the same thing
but I think that is
sufficient and we know not to do it
right brother Dre sir yes sir thank you
thank you for that let's move on to our
next question yes time
8:15 um Zion asks why did Jesus choose
Judas es scaria to be one of his
disciples if he knew he would betray him
did that have to happen in order for the
scripture to be
fulfilled all right guest caller can you
shine some light on
that but one thing is I ain't going to
ever answer a question on why did Jesus
do
something I'm too scared to do that
however I will tell you that he knew
that uh uh uh uh who was going to betray
him that he had to be betrayed first
let's go into acts the 2 chapter read
verses 22 and
23 acts the 2
chapter 20 22 and 23 when you get there
brother
tanzel ye men of Israel hear these words
Jesus of Nazareth a man approved of God
among you by Miracles and wonders and
signs which God did by him in the midst
of you as you yourselves also
know him being delivered by the
determined determined counsel and for
knowledge of God ye have taken and by
Wicked hands have crucify ified and
slain now let let you know that uh he he
been delivered by full full knowledge if
uh you know and and counsel of God so he
knew he had to be betrayed right and he
knew that J Judas was going betray him
and let's go into Psalms chapter 41 and
read verse
9 Psalms 41
verse
n yeah my own familiar friend in whom I
trust which did eat of my bread have
lifted up his heel against
me so now you know when Jesus said
somebody going to betray me and his
disciples start asking who and he said
the one that stops with
me put it up there and Judah sh with it
so he knew do
and it was determined prophecy had to be
fulfilled but I don't but I don't dare
said try to figure out you answer why
Jesus did
something that's that's that's uh uh
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question next
question yes time
8:17 Malik secure says in the Kingdom
will we have a family like we do now is
is there anywhere in the Bible that
speaks about those things Jerome what
you
say Yeah in the son's Kingdom you know
you g to have Flesh and Blood beings and
you gonna have Spirit beings the Flesh
and Blood beings they going to have
family just like we do now but not the
spirit beings because the spirit beings
that come up in the first resurrection
they're not given in marriage and they
won't be having any children okay but
let's go to Ezekiel chapter
37 and um pick it up at verse 24 read to
the
25 Ezekiel
37 yeah verse 24 through 25 and then
we're gonna
Skip and David my servant shall be king
over them and they sh they all shall
have one Shepherd and they shall all
walk in my judgment and observe my my
statues and do them and they shall dwell
in the land that I have given unto Jacob
my servant wherein your fathers have
dwelt they shall dwell therein even they
and their children and their children's
children ever and my servant David shall
be their prince forever yeah at this
time David would have been resurrected
he's gonna be resurrected from the dead
to be king over the children of Israel
forever skip down to verse 28 the Lord
going to dwell in the midst of the
children of Israel Forever at this time
read verse 28 and the Heathen shall know
that I the Lord do sanctify Israel for
My Sanctuary shall be in the midst of
them forever
more yeah now let's go to um
Luke CU When the Lord return let's go to
uh Luke Chapter 20 and read verse 34
through through 36
when you get it go ahead and
read and Jesus answered and said unto
them the children of this world Mary and
are given in marriage but they which
shall be accounted worthy to obtain that
world and the resurrection from the dead
neither Mary nor I given in marriage oh
yeah
36 neither can they die anymore for they
are equal unto the angels and are the
children of God being the children of
the Resurrection yeah so when those that
come up in that first
resurrection and those that come up in
that second Resurrection they ain't
going to have children no more they're
not going to have no families and stuff
but in the son's Kingdom during that
thousand
years they gonna have the Flesh and
Blood people they going to be having
children they going to be having family
they're goingon to be married like we do
now
that's all I got on
me all right thank you for that as we
continue to move on next question yes uh
Eve Davy asks is there a scripture that
says that if a woman is married her
husband is her head
covering yeah there's a couple of
scriptures that say that Adam was e head
covering and so thus it traveled down
throughout the generation
let's go to 1 Corinthians 11 chapter 1
Corinthians
11 and when you get there brother Tel I
want you to read
that one verse for me and then we're
going to go into Ephesians 5 go ahead
with that 1 Corinthians 11
and3 but I will have you know that the
head of every man is Christ and the head
of the woman is the man and the head of
Christ
is God so there we go with a protocol
God is the head of the man the man is
the head of the woman now turn over to
Ephesians 5 right quick Ephesians 5
epesi
5 and when you get there let's pick it
up at that verse uh
22 and go ahead and read for me brother
wives submit yourselves unto your own
husbands as unto the Lord
yes for the husband is the head of the
wife even as Christ is the head of the
church and he is the savior of the body
go ahead therefore after the church is
subject unto Christ so let the wives be
to their own husbands and everything and
the husband got a responsibility too 25
husbands love your wife even as Christ
also loved the church and gave himself
for it yes skip down read 28 that'll be
it so are men to love their wives as
their own bodies and he that loveth his
wife loveth himself yes so the man's
required to play a role the woman is
required to play a role and God is the
head over both but yeah those are some
scriptures that says that the man is the
head of the wife that's all I
got hope that that answer your question
next question sister next question
Pamela angland says who are the two
witnesses R tell us something about who
are these two
witnesses all the two witnesses are
definitely absolutely not Spirit beings
because when you read the prophecy of
the two witnesses they're G to be killed
and spirit beings can't be killed so
let's go take a look at it um
Revelations
11 and we pick it up at verse three and
we going to skip to verse
7 this is talking about what's going to
happen um during the time of the uh
Great Tribulation for three and a half
years and there prophecy is within that
time
span okay when you get it go ahead and
read and I will give power unto my two
witnesses and they shall prophesies 1,23
score days close
sa that's and half years skip down to
verse S read to
the and when they shall have finished
their testimony the Beast that ascendeth
out of the bottom of his pit shall make
war against them and shall overcome them
and kill them and their dead bodies
shall lie in the streets of the great
city which spiritually is called Sodom
in Egypt where also our Lord was
crucified yeah so that proves that they
they flesh they gonna be flesh and blood
men now I turn it over to the panel
because I don't know who they might be
but I know they Flesh and Blood being
and they not spirit being that's all I
got on the simple answer to that
question is we don't know
okay all right and we're gonna keep it
moving from there to our next question
keeping it moving Zion says what if I
have to work on the Sabbath should I
quit my job or find another job with
lower pay while I'm at work I still tune
into the online savath
classes all right well can't tell you to
quit your job for no lower pay you know
because if a man don't or woman don't
work don't work they don't eat but um I
think you should try and pray that the
Lord give you the Sabbath day um it's
good you listening to the class is when
you're at work open to the panel for
anything
extra now you don't quit your job if you
ain't got no way to eat like you said
you have to eat but the whole thing is
you pray to the Lord to give you a
better job yeah but until that time come
it's just like Jesus said you oxes fall
into the well you got to do what you got
to do but uh don't quit your job try you
you pray to the Lord to uh give you a
better job don't have to be a little pay
if you going to go ask him to give you
one with more pay right
right
too
okay all right and keep listening and
enjoying them Sabbath day lessons all
right next question next question Johnny
O ask is it okay to study the Apocrypha
with the KJV
Bible yes call with the Apocrypha and
the
KJV share some light I tell you listen
you read whatever you want that is up to
you but uh I'm going to tell you what
book you going to be judged out
of let's go to Revelation 20th chapter
and read verse 11 and
12 now saw our great white Throne to him
that sat on it from whose face the earth
and the heaven fled away and there was
found no place for them and I saw the
dead small and great stand before God
and the books were open and another book
was open which is The Book of Life and
the dead were judge out of those things
which were written in the books
according to their
works now that's what you going to be
judged out of this Bible that you have
as far as the Apocrypha concerned I have
read some of the Apocrypha and some of
the stuff that said in there let me know
that uh it's not legitimate
and you can't find out or it's
authent who how to make it what do they
call it is not
authenticated then why should you read
something that have no benefit what you
should read is the book that you going
to be judged out of and that is this
holy King James version that you have in
front of
you all I have to say that is correct
these 66 books of the King James Bible
is all you need for
salvation hope that answered your
question sister Deborah let's go in a
new territory uh yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday September
the 25th
2024 Adam asked will you please explain
Hebrews 5 verse 13 there have been times
where I mention the Book of Genesis or
Exodus to a friend and they would tell
me that's just milk as if that's not
good
enough all right Hebrews 5 and13 is
where they start right de yes okay guest
caller can you share some light let's go
to Hebrews 5 and 13
10 and read
it
right for everyone that uses milk is
unskillful in the word of righteousness
but for he is a
b
now so they going to call
Genesis milk and exodus
milk those are Genesis Exodus and the
rest of the Old Testament those that's
prophecy now let me show you what the uh
uh uh what the book said concerning
prophecy let's go into
Hebrews fth chapter
and read verse 12 and
13 read it when you get there Hebrews 5
12 and
13 yes 12 and
13 for when for when for the time ye
ought to be teachers ye have need that
one teach you again which be the
principle of the Oracles of God and I
become such as have need of milk and not
of strong
meat now this is talking about he's
talking to some people that look they uh
uh uh people that don't have no
understanding you know uh uh uh and
that's why he let you let you know that
these people don't have understanding
because anybody that have understanding
you know that
Genesis and
Exodus is not milk let me show you what
Peter did you finish that 13th verse no
we at 13 Now read for everyone that usth
milk is unskillful in the word of
righteousness for he is
aey now all Paul all Paul is telling you
is telling these people that that
apparently didn't have no understanding
because he said look when you're
supposed to be teaching well you should
be teaching you're a student do you milk
but anybody that said Genesis and and
exodus is milk they are the ones that uh
on milk and they don't have the
knowledge to make that statement let me
show you what the Lord said about
prophecy at Peter say let's go into
second Peter the first chapter read
verses 19-
21 but we have also a more sure word of
Prophecy where unto
uh second Peter uh
one second Peter 1 verse
19 well start where he said that we have
not devised conly fables 16
16 but we have not
F now this is Peter them that walked
around with Jesus so look what Peter
said go ahead we have not followed
Connie devis favor
when we made known unto you the power
and coming of our Lord Jesus Christ but
were eyewitnesses of his
majesty now he let you know that they
were eyewitnesses they walk around with
Jesus but keep
reading for he received from God the
Father honor and Glory when there came
such a voice to him from the excellent
SE Glory this is my beloved Son in whom
I am well
pleased and this voice which came from
heaven we heard when we were with him in
the Holy
mouth we have also a more sure word of
Prophecy where unto listen what list
what he said now but we are but now we
have also a more sure word of Prophecy
that mean the prophecy the word is more
sure than what Peter them was dealing
with we also have a most sure word of
Prophecy keep
reading where un ye do well that you
take heed as unto a light that shineth
in the dark place until the day Dawn and
the day star arise in your
hearts but knowing this first that no
Prophecy of the scripture is of any
private
interpretation but the prophecy came not
in Old Time by the will of man but holy
men of God spake as they were moved by
the Holy
Ghost now Peter the one that the Lord
left the keys to did that we have a most
sure word of Prophecy cuz he understood
that all these prophets spoke that they
was moved by the Holy Ghost but then
let's go and look at G let's go into
Revelation 19th Chapter and read verse
10 Revelation
19 and
10 and I fell at his feet to worship him
and he said unto me see thou do it I am
thy fellow servant and of thy Brethren
that have the testimony of Jesus worship
God for the testimony of Jesus is the
spirit of
Prophecy now if the testimony of Jesus
is a spirit of Prophecy which is the
word of Prophecy then I guess then uh
Jesus is dealing with milk too
huh maybe the people that said that to
you are the ones that's on milk that's
all I have to say
all right so let your friend know that
he stand corrected with the scriptures
all right let's move on to our next
question yes Valencia wants you to
explain James 5 verses
4-6 what you say Dre yeah let's go to
James
5 and um I want you to read verse one
first Tel and then we'll go down and
read 4 through six
go ahead when you get it
brother go to now ye rich men weeping
high for your miseries that shall come
upon you so he talking about these rich
men that they should weep and howl
because these miseries is GNA come upon
them skip down to verse
four behold the high of the labors who
have reaped down your fields which is if
you kept back by fraud crier and the
cries of them which have reap are enter
into the ears of the Lord of
sabath saot and ye have lived in ye have
lived in pleas pleasure on the earth and
been wanted but you have nourished your
hearts as in the day of
Slaughter so these these rich men this
rich man hired laborers to re down their
fears and they held back by fra what was
due to the laborers and the laborers
cried out to the
Lord and Lord of the Sabbath heard them
and they live these rich men lived in
pleasure on the earth and they were
cruel because that's what wanton meant
and he said you have in verse six you
condemn and kill the innocent and and
they didn't resist you but let's go to
Malachi 3 and we going to read verse 5
Malachi 3 and verse five this is what
the Lord is g to deal with with folks
that do people like
this go ahead Malachi 3 and5 read it
when you get it brother and I will come
near to you I will come near to you to
judg me and I will be a swift witness
against the s ERS and against the
adulterers and against false wearers and
against those that oppressed the hirling
in his wages the W the fatherless and
that turn aside the stranger from his
right and fear not me say the Lord of
hosts so what what was happening right
there they were oppressing the people
that they hired in their
wages but is going to be a swift witness
against them they cried out to the Lord
and the Lord
heard that's
it all right thank you for that brother
hope that ansed your question as we move
on with the time check yes the time is
8:38 moving on Jackie Lamar asks can a
man listen to the word talking about iog
lesson while daily working outside with
his head covered
oh you shouldn't do that but let's go uh
let's turn back quickly to Psalms 19
tanzel because this word of God is
sweeter than honey and the
honeycomb pick it up in verse seven
brother Psalms 19 and7 go
ahead the law the Lord is
perfect the soul the testimony testimony
of the Lord is making wise the simple y
statues of the Lord are right rejoicing
the heart the Commandments the
Commandments of the Lord is pure
enlightening the
eyes and the fear of the Lord is clean
and doing forever the Judgment of the
Lords are true and righteous all
together some holy word we reading here
go ahead brother one last verse more to
be desired are they than gold yeah than
much fine gold sweeter also than honey
and the hone uhuh read 11 while we there
moreover by them is thy servant Warn and
in keeping of them there is great reward
great reward now turn over to 1
Corinthians 11 1 Corinthians
11 and when you get there brother read
that verse four for
me four and five we're going to we're
going to go ahead put the woman in there
too since we get these questions all the
time read four and
five every man praying or prophesying
having his head cover desor of his head
so even when you when you talking the
word of God when you listening when you
reading the true word hey you should
have your head uncovered if you're a
brother and what about the sisters but
every woman that pray or prophesy with
her head uncovered design her head for
that is even all one as is as if she was
shaven yep and that is what the word of
God say that's all I
got well I I got to throw something in
there yes sir he said praying praying to
prophesy you listening if you listening
make sure you ain't praying or
prophesying
okay all right all right then youre make
sure you ain't praying or prophesying
you just
listening that's all I have to say
okay all right we're gonna move on to
our next question sister moving on
Lander says in both Mark 16 ver
9-20 and 1 John 5: 7 and 8 there are
verses that many scholars believe were
added later and not found in the
earliest
manuscripts how should we approach and
interpret these addition
okay in that verse uh Mark
169 verse 20 through 20 9 through 20 9
through 20 okay we ask the guest caller
because they asking about scholars in
this question here Mark
16 and guest caller can you take it from
there sure it's not no this wasn't
something added
it was just something that was wrongly
punctuated let's go and we ain't going
to read all of that uh uh all of this
but uh let's just go read some of
it 16 and let's let's uh look at the
uh let's look at verse at verse start at
verse 9 and let's look at how it read
okay
yep now when Jesus was risen early the
first day of the week he appeared first
to Mary Magdalene out of whom he had
cast Seven
Devils he let me stop it here let me
stop it here first thing was is the
punctuation when Jesus risen
early pal
simola when Jesus was R risen rather
that's when she had K semic right behind
the wood
rizle early the first day of the week
week he appeared first to Mar Magdalene
and Jesus did appear to her early the
first day of the week but it wasn't but
it it was
a he had already risen right he rose
early on the first day of the week what
he saying was that he had already risen
and and uh uh uh so when he had risen he
appeared to Mary Magdalene early on the
first day of the week to let you know
that uh uh uh uh uh that what this is
talking
about let's go let's go and read
something here let's go into St John the
20th
chapter and read we going to read 1
through three and we going to skip St
John 20 1
23 read it when you get
there the first day of the week cometh
magdaline early when it was yet dark
unto the SE sepet which seeth the stone
taken away from the
sepet then she run up and cometh to
Simon Peter and to the other disciples
whom Jesus love and said unto them they
have taken away the Lord out of the sep
and we know not where they have laid him
and so she ran so she ran and told them
CU when she got there was still do he
was gone go ahead what did verse three
did you finish verse three we had verse
three and Peter therefore went
forth and that other disciple and came
to the
septier N when they went they saw that
he was gone so they eventually left Skip
and let's see what happen skip down to
verse 10 read verse 10 and
11 then the disciples went away again
unto their own homes but Mary stood
without thou at the septic weeping and
as she wept she stooped down and looked
unto the
septica now give down to verse six did
you finish that verse
11 skip down to verse 16 and read verse
16 and
17 and Jesus said unto her Mary and she
turned herself and said unto him rabona
which is the say master and Jesus said
unto her touch me not for I am not yet
ascended to my father but go to my
brethren and say unto them I Ascend it
unto my father and your father and to my
God and your God yep now she talked to
him it was still early CU once she got
there it was still dark she get when he
got they came and they left it was still
early in the morning it didn't say he
rose early in the morning what he saying
is after he had
risen early that same day he talked to
Mary
you know so that's all it's saying not
just saying because the punctuation is
wrong you going to say well you know
look like Jesus rules that uh uh how did
it start out in the in the ninth verse
not Jesus was
risen look at the word to what was said
was
risen that mean he was already that mean
he's already done it happening MH yeah
come heard the first day of the week he
appeared to
marry same time but he had already risen
right so that coincide with the rest of
what's written and we don't have to read
no further because uh it is a punctation
problem concerning this but now there
was the second part of this question
here uh yes they also gave uh first John
5: 7 and
eight well let's go read
it three to Bear
witness go and read
it first
John 57
and8 for there are three that bear
record in heaven the Father the word and
the Holy Ghost and these three are one
and there are this now let's deal with
this one first okay there are three that
b record in heaven the
father what it
say word and and the Holy
Ghost now let's go to re first chapter
and read that Revelation 1 and we're
going to read Revelation start at verse
one the revelation of Jesus Christ which
God gave unto him
now the revelation of Jesus Christ Jesus
is one ain't it isn't that
correct God gave to him that's two isn't
that correct
correct go ahead to show unto his
servants things which must surely come
to
pass and he send signified it by his
angels unto his servant
John finish it who bear record of the
word of God and of the testimony of
Jesus Christ and of all things that he
saw do now the father bear record he
gave it to Jesus the son he bear record
then Jesus gave it to the Angel and the
angel bear record those are the three in
heaven and when he got to John there
John was in the earth so he B record of
the same thing and testimony of Jesus is
that correct
right so the three that b record is God
the Father God the son and a ministering
Spirit a serving Spirit which is an
angel in this case Gabriel those are the
three that bad record in heaven now read
the eth verse go back to first uh uh
uh John let's go back to read verse
verse eight go
ahead and there are three that bear
witness in Earth the spirit uhuh and the
water and the blood and these three
agree in one
let's look at these three that be that
uh uh that uh agree uh in the earth
first thing is we going to deal with
what said the spirit
right go go to St John 6 and read 63
verse
63 it is the spirit that Quicken the
flesh profited nothing the words that I
speak unto you they are
Spirit they are life so now first thing
you got to have is the word of
God words that Spirit profit nothing the
words that I speak unto you they are
spirit and they are life so so skip down
and read verse 66-
68 from that time any of his disciples
went back and walked no more with
him then said Jesus unto the 12 will he
also go away then Simon Peter answer him
Lord to whom shall we go thou H has the
words of eternal
life so
now the first part it is the spirit
which is the word you got to have the
word cuz if you don't hear the word of
God how can you obey him right and this
words of spirit now let's go to the
second one what was the second one
water the water let's go into
Mark 16 chapter read verses 15 and
16 and he said unto them go ye into the
all the world and preach the gospel to
Every Creature he that believeth and is
baptized shall be saved he that
believeth not shall be
damned so you got to have the word right
and you got to be baptized ain't that
correct in
water all right now let's deal with the
third one what was the third one
Blood let's go into Revelation the 5th
chapter read verses 8 and
N Revelation
five Revelation Revelation five 8 and n
right yep and when he had taken the book
four be and 4 and 20 Elders fell down
before the
lamb having every one of them hars and
golden vows full of oders which are the
prayers of
saints and they sang a new song saying
thou are worthy to take the book and to
open the seals thereof for thou was
slain and H has redeemed us to God by
thy blood out of every country and
tongue and people and nation and has
made
us finish it and has made us unto our
God Kings and Priests and we shall reign
on the
earth now if you going to be recovered
from the sins that Adam and Eve brought
upon us you have to be Redeemed by the
blood ain't that correct that's corre so
the spirit first is the word you got to
have the word once you get the word then
you got to be baptized in Jesus name now
once you baptized then you are under the
Covenant you are under the blood like it
said in uh uh uh Galatians the thir
chapter he has been baptized in Christ
and put on
Christ all the children of God through
Christ and if you be Christ then you
Abraham seed and air according to the
promise so you got to handle the word
first so you know what to do then you
got to be
baptized because that is uh uh represent
the uh uh newness you know you died the
old man died and the righteous man rules
like Jesus rules God and then the last
one is you got to be under the blood
those are the
three that
uh record in the
earth that's all I have to say yes sir I
hope that uh your question is we
continue to move on der time is a ticket
yes Jun
norford ask in Luke 2 verse
33-35 in verse 35 is this sword the word
of God and why is it piercing Mary's
Soul all right brother Julius go
ahead this is talking about when Jesus
appears the soul
because a mother watching her child
being
crucified the fulfill the prophecy
fulfill the prophecy so uh let's go to
Luke the 23rd
chapter Luke
23 cuz it was always a great company
that was following Jesus especially a
lot and a lot of women including his
mother Luke 23 and pick this up at verse
26 Luke 23 and
26 that sword represents the hurt and
the pain of watching your child suffer
Luke 23 and 26 when you get it go ahead
and as they led him away they LED hold
upon one Simon of syan coming out of the
country and on him they laid the cross
that he might bear it after Jesus uhhuh
and there follow him a great company of
people and a woman which also bewell and
the minuted him they did
what they bewailed and lamented him
because it hurt them to see him being
whooped spit up
beat crown of Thor pushed into your head
how could your mother not how could her
soul not be pierced right right
suffer she watched her son suffer so
that's all this is saying is just like
Zechariah 12 told you you going uh uh uh
those that pierce him shall mourn as if
they lost her only
son so it was Heavy uh lamentation heavy
grieving including his mother that's all
I got on that Cornell yes sir so that's
that sword that that's that sword that
pierced our soul the hurt and pain and
anger of watching her son be
crucified yep he did it for the love out
of love for the sins of the whole world
that's right all right brother thank you
for that sister Deborah next one yes
charot t uh says if there is only one
resurrection of Christ Second Coming
what took place in Matthew when Christ
died on the cross all right you're
probably talking about when old people
came out the grave after his
resurrection but let's go into Matthew
27 since you didn't put a number there
let's see Matthew 27 what happened when
these people came out of the
grave and let's read it let's read it
tanzel let's pick it up where that the
Lord had died here and let's see what
happened go straight to verse 50 and
read down for me go ahead Jesus when he
had cried again with a
voice yielded up the ghost yep and
behold the veil of the temple was
written Twain from the top of the bottom
and the Earth did quake and the Rocks
ran uhhuh the graves were open and many
bodies of the saints were slep a ro
uhhuh and came out of the graves after
his resurrection and went into the holy
city and appeared unto many so these
people came out of the Grave after his
resurrection he came out first and these
people came out after but all these
people died again they went back to the
grave but he was showing his power so
let's go into our first Thessalonians
the 4th chapter and let's
see when people are going to come out of
the grav again and this time on a
permanent basis for this first
resurrection first Thessalonians 4 when
you get there brother pick it up at that
verse 6
uh 15 and read down go
ahead but this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord that we which are alive
and remain unto the coming of the Lord
shall not prevent them which are asleep
those that have died go ahead for the
Lord himself shall descend from heaven
with the Shout with the voice of the
arch angel and with the Trump of God and
the dead in Christ shall rise
first then we which are are alive and
remain shall be caught up together with
them in the clouds to meet the Lord in
the air and so shall we ever be with the
Lord so those people that died again hey
they went they came out the grave they
died again and this is what making the
cut is all about in their first
resurrection then the Lord go call them
out and so shall they ever be with the
Lord as we come back down to earth
sister Deb let's get uh this last
question in and that'll be time for us
go ahead all right uh do Martin asks
what is the Nephilim I just saw a movie
called The Watchers and I think it was
referring to the Nephilim brother Dre
what you say yeah I don't know about the
movie to watch us and in terms of
Nephilim that's a term that that
somebody called talking about these are
Fallen Angels is not biblical
they go to Genesis the 6th chapter and
they say that Angels married women that
is not biblical that is not in Genesis
6 Angels do not marry nor are they given
in
marriage in the book that they like to
go to to talk about it which is one of
those Lost Books it talks
about somebody coming out of a woman's
womb that's 5 feet
tall
3,000 and 3,000
eels is
4,500 feet tall now how in the world can
a baby come out of a 5 foot woman
4,500 feet tall that's taller than the
tallest building on this
planet let's go to uh Matthew 22 and
read verse
30 Matthew 22 and read verse3 go ahead
and read it when you get it brother for
in the resurrection they for in the
resurrection they neither marry nor I
given in marriage but are as the angels
of God in heaven because the Angels do
not marri nor are they given in
marriage you can't read that
and in Genesis 6 this is talking about
those that left from serving God it is
it don't have nothing to do with angels
sleeping with
women that's a concoction that they made
up a myth right please do not believe
that right a fable brother Drake yes sir
all right thank you for that brother and
we hope that answer question sister
Deborah time chck the time is
9:02 all right we have come to the end
of the show we want to thank everybody
who joined us from all around the world
sent in those
questions and we took joy and answering
them and we asking you that if you
submitted a question and we didn't have
a chance to get to it please don't
resubmit it sister Deborah would take
your question put it in rotation and we
will answer it next Wednesday at the
same time so we want to thank you all
and until we come together again be safe
out there be blessed and may the Lord
have mercy on us all close us out
brother
tanzel Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done done in earth as it is
in heaven give us this day our daily
bread and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debt to us and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
for thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever in Jesus name we
pray amen amen amen